{
    "subject": "resource/Vasa_IFK",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Football_clubs_in_Finland",
    "human_readable": "Vasa IFK is about Football clubs in Finland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9865368604660034,
            "question": "Is Vasa IFK a football club from Finland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927199006080627,
            "question": "Where are the football clubs in Finland typically located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7296434044837952,
            "question": "Can you name some famous Finnish football clubs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6429274082183838,
            "question": "What are the typical characteristics of a successful football club in Finland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368963122367859,
            "question": "What sport is Vasa IFK associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229851245880127,
            "question": "Are there any regional differences in Finnish football clubs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5878859162330627,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing Finnish football clubs today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5352942943572998,
            "question": "What other information might be included about Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5005531311035156,
            "question": "How popular is football in Finland compared to other sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17825515568256378,
            "question": "Does Vasa IFK have a website or social media presence?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vasa IFK is about Football clubs in Finland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_246_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular is football in Finland compared to other sports?",
            "html": "dbpedia_246_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other information might be included about Vasa IFK?",
            "html": "dbpedia_246_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges facing Finnish football clubs today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_246_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_246_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided, particularly from the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_246/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt`, which discusses Vasa IFK as a football club in Finland associated with the broader context of IFK clubs and their historical significance in Finnish football."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}